<idea-plugin>
    <description><![CDATA[
        <p>
            Plugin for LaTeX and BibTeX support in IntelliJ.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Syntax highlighting</li>
            <li>Autocompletion of labels, (custom defined and package defined) commands and environments</li>
            <li>Writer ergonomics - writing LaTeX made less cumbersome</li>
            <li>Compiler support for pdfLaTeX, LuaTeX, Latexmk, texliveonfly, XeLaTeX, bibtex, and biber</li>
            <li>Inspections. Intentions. And heaps more inspections</li>
            <li>Full BibTeX support</li>
            <li>Formatter for LaTeX and BibTeX</li>
            <li>Structure view for LaTeX and BibTeX with filters</li>
            <li>Code folding for imports, sections, and environments</li>
            <li>Built-in pdf viewer via the PDF Viewer plugin, including forward and backward search</li>
            <li>SumatraPDF (Windows), Evince (Linux), Okular (Linux) and Skim (MacOS) support with forward and backward search</li>
            <li>Smart quotes</li>
            <li>Unicode math preview</li>
            <li>Equation and TikZ picture preview</li>
            <li>Gutter icons for quick compilation and file includes</li>
            <li>Fancy icons that fit in with the IntelliJ style</li>
            <li>Brace matching</li>
            <li>Word counting tool</li>
            <li>File templates for <code>.tex</code>, <code>.sty</code>, <code>.cls</code>, <code>.bib</code>, and <code>.tikz</code> files</li>
            <li>Automagically import packages of common commands</li>
            <li>Go to declaration of labels</li>
            <li>Shortcuts for styling text</li>
            <li>Line commenter</li>
            <li>Support for user-created document classes and packages</li>
            <li>Toggle star action</li>
            <li>Words of encouragement</li>
            <li>A complete feature list can be found at our <a href="https://github.com/Hannah-Sten/TeXiFy-IDEA/wiki/Features">wiki</a> (work in progress).</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            All critique, questions, suggestions, requests, bug reports, kudos, and (non-)creative ideas are
            welcome on the <a href="https://github.com/Hannah-Sten/TeXiFy-IDEA">plugin's GitHub page</a>.
            If you want to directly chat with us, take a peek at the project's
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#TeXiFy-IDEA_Support:gitter.im">gitter</a>.
            If you like the project, please <a href="https://www.paypal.me/HannahSchellekens">donate</a> to support ongoing development!
        </p>
    ]]></description>
</idea-plugin>